Good morning, Mr. Scout.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten, 11, 12.
Thirty-two, 33, 34,
35, 36, thirty-se--
Okay, me and Helly will find the goat man
and other possible goat people.
Dylan, hit the new break room.
Maybe some of
the other departments use it too.
Yeah. Maybe later.
Okay. This is kind of important, Dylan.
Yeah. I'm in a good groove here,
but don't worry about it. I'll get to it.
Okay. Well, just show them the sketch.
Do not leave it behind.
O&D.
Yes, Irv. You can do this.
I know.
You guys really think
they're gonna let us roam around?
They said on the video
we can go wherever we want.
Lumon is listening, remember?
I thought that meant
they were listening to our conversations.
Yeah, he's right, Mark.
I did get the hint of a double meaning.
Well, be discreet.
If they don't know we're doing it,
how can they punish us?
Hey,
you haven't been back there, have you?
No, no.
We've got you.
Thank you, Helly.
So, say we find her...
Sorry?
Say we get to the goat department
and they're like,
"Yes, Ms. Casey's here.
She's in this goat cage."
What do we do then?
Well, we get her to the south stairwell...
I'll go with her...
and once we're out the door,
my outie'll know what to do.
Right. Okay. Well,
sounds like you've got it figured out.
Are you sure you're okay
helping me out with this?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, good.
Yeah.
I... I...
Dylan.
I thought you were going to O&D.
I've recreated the paintings.
The ones I told you about.
The ones my outie was working on.
What?
You see, I've been thinking.
Maybe the hallway is really down here.
Maybe that's what my dreams have been.
We could look for it, Dylan.
We could go today.
You could accompany me.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe.
Or maybe you go yourself,
like, for stealth, you know?
- Stealth?
- Yeah.
Look, I can't really explain. I just--
Miss Huang.
Hall pass.
Everything chill?
Dylan G., come with me, please.
Good morning, Seth.
Natalie.
Looks like your balloons
could use some coffee.
- They were in the--
- I've got the Board.
Of course.
Hello.
The Board says, "Hello."
Hello. I want to thank the Board humbly
for my recent betterment.
The Board says, "You're welcome."
The Board is jubilant at your ascendance.
It wants you to feel appreciated
and asks if you do.
I do.
The Board austerely desires for you
to feel connected to Lumon's history.
To that end,
please accept from the Board these
inclusively re-canonicalized paintings
intended to help you see yourself
in Kier, our founder.
Oh, my.
You'll find the whole Kier cycle.
The Board wishes to express
that I, Natalie,
received the same gift
upon receipt of my current position
and found it extremely moving.
I'm grateful.
Yes.
It's meaningful
to see myself reflected in...
The Board has concluded the call.
Congratulations, Seth.
Is that it?
Think so.
You're gonna--
You sure?
Okay.
All right. Okay, we're doing this.
Can you see anything?
No. Careful, there's poop.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
What the hell?
Are you here to kill me?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I... Sorry. Hi, I'm Mark.
- I'm Helly.
- And we're with Macrodata Refinement.
What is this place?
Mammalians Nurturable.
Please, we mean you no harm.
We just wanna talk.
Please.
Irving.
Felicia, hello.
I'm sorry to pop in after all this time.
I'm sure you must be very busy.
It's good to see you.
Her name's Ms. Casey.
She's our former Wellness Director.
Wellness...
we don't abide such fripperies here.
Right. Well, she's been retired, but
we believe she may still be on the floor.
Are you sure you don't know her?
Maybe you should take that page
of paper and be on your way.
Not until you've answered my question.
Mark.
You should have left.
It would be cool to know
what this is about.
So, like, is it rude to keep asking
why you're a kid?
I don't mean to impugn.
It's just like, are you okay, you know?
They're not, like,
forcing you to be here, are they?
Oh, fuck.
Why are we going to the security room?
Wow.
Dylan?
Hi.
Dylan G.,
through good behavior and output,
you've earned an 18-minute
visitation event with your outie's wife,
Gretchen G.
Cool.
Your time begins now.
Should we sit?
Nice sack.
Sorry?
Your... The--
Thanks. They made me put my stuff in here.
Badass.
You really don't know me at all?
No. Well, I mean,
from the photos from just now, but...
Yeah, Seth warned me
that this might be weird.
- Who's Seth?
- Don't you--
Please refrain from sharing information
that may be privileged or sensitive.
Thank you.
Okay.
Who is that child?
Miss Huang.
Look. It's really nice to meet you,
but am I in trouble?
Oh, no. No, you're not in trouble.
We have three kids.
Right.
And you...
No, he... Or--
My husband has had trouble
keeping other jobs.
He dumb?
No.
He a dick?
What is wrong with him?
Nothing's wrong with him.
He just...
He never quite found his thing.
So he's actually kind of a fuck up?
Do you wanna see a picture of the kids?
Yeah.
Okay.
So, Jim is six.
He's in the first grade now.
And Ruth is four.
And Merrick just turned two.
Wow.
Holy shit.
Look at them.
They're awesome.
They are.
And we live on a cattle ranch?
And then... And Burt says,
"I don't care if
you're Baird goddamn Eagan,
you don't come to my department
and tell me how to print a snow globe."
I ca... My God, he was fearless.
I worked with Burt for six years.
And I only ever saw him
scared of one thing.
He spent two hours on his hair
the first time he went to visit you.
Really?
I should show you something.
- If we see her--
- Not her. It's a...
Here.
Oh, Irving, it's lovely.
I'd draw one every day I couldn't see him.
My numbers went down,
but I didn't even care.
Oh, no. That's not Burt.
That's something else.
That's just a... That's nothing.
It's...
How do you know about the exports hall?
I'm sorry?
We send a lot of shipments there.
Used to go ourselves.
But now, they send a guy.
Do you remember where it is?
Hello.
Hi.
- Excuse me. Have you seen this woman?
- Hey! Stop that!
Her name's Ms. Casey.
She was the Wellness director.
- Stop that!
- Have any of you seen her?
Enough! We've decided to send a courier
to inform Mr. Milchick of your inquiry.
No. You can't do that.
They could kill her if they find out--
That's not a Mammalians problem.
It's an innie problem.
Listen, we used to be afraid of
other departments too--
We're not afraid of you.
Look, they just disappeared her.
And if we let this happen to Ms. Casey,
then who's gonna step up
when it happens to us?
If one of your goats went missing,
wouldn't you go looking for it?
She used to come do her sessions
in our husbandry tanks.
She had a gentle way about her.
She said my outie excels at stargazing.
Meant a great deal to me.
As far as we know,
she was retired, just like they say.
But if you suspect otherwise,
we won't hinder your search.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
But before you go, we would...
like to see your bellies.
Our bellies?
Please.
Okay.
See? Pouchless.
Proves nothing.
Okay. Let's--
- So we'll just... Yeah.
- Yeah.
I'm glad we did this.
I mean, I hope, for you, this was...
I don't know.
Yeah, it was.
And I'll be good.
I'm gonna make you all proud.
I'm always proud of you, Dylan.
Cool.
I love you.
Sorry.
- Habit.
- No, it's...
Okay.
All right.
- Bye.
- Yeah.
So remember Merrick's ear thing, okay?
Copy that.
- Left ear.
- Yep.
And did you do the cookies
for Jim's class?
Bye.
It's our week for cookies.
I did not do the cookies. Sorry.
So, it's a tube
and you just need to slice them
- and then you put them in the oven.
- Got it, yeah.
Love you.
Hey, how was the thing?
What thing?
The thing with me.
Yeah, it was good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Weird good, but good.
Cool.
Yeah. Okay. Okay, okay.
I'll see you in the morning.
- Bye.
"But surely beer and juleps
cannot fill the void left by love.
Indeed, only wine can achieve this,
but it is famously costly,
which is why sadness is among the most
recurrent issues facing the poor."
Remarkable. So astute.
Is it? That's what I was going for.
Hi.
My babe.
This is Natalie Kalen from Lumon.
Is everything okay?
Yes. God, yes.
Natalie just stopped by
to discuss my book, actually.
It's a joy to meet you, Devon.
You must be so proud.
I am.
I'm sure you know by now
that your husband's work
has found its way onto our severed floor.
Yeah. Do we know how that happened yet?
So we've actually moved beyond that,
and we are now discussing the--
What was the term you used?
- The result.
Ricken's words have had a profound effect
upon our workers.
We think he's really tapped
into something.
And Natalie wants to discuss
a version of The You You Are,
specifically for innies.
Okay, well, that's cool. I mean,
but what's wrong with the current version?
Nothing.
No, the explanation
is actually very interesting.
It's fascinating, actually. You, please.
There's a certain verbiage
to which innies respond more favorably.
If we just tweak it here and there.
They think that it could be
a real game changer.
Gotcha.
I gotta go.
But she needs a bottle in an hour. So...
Of course.
- Devon.
- Yes?
Can I just say, your brother is one of
the sweetest members of our severed team.
Yeah, he's a good egg.
Okay. One hour.
So she said her name's Natalie?
Natalie Kalen, I think.
What... Was she asking,
like, what I'm up to or--
Nope, 'cause it's Ricken they're after.
- Ricken?
- Yep. His book.
What?
I guess you and your work friends
were so inspired by it.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- Yep.
That they're... They wanna do
like an innie specific cut.
Wow, okay. Well, there's just...
There's a lot I'm not gonna say.
And that is so appreciated.
Have you told Ricken
what we're doing here?
- Are you insane? No.
- Okay.
Good.
Okay, so you need to see the afterimage
for, like, two and a half minutes?
Two minutes, 18 seconds.
It's from the parking spot
to the elevator, give or take.
Yeah, I think the Whole Mind Collective
would be very proud of this.
As well as your kindergarten teacher.
What the fuck was her name?
Mrs. Lustgarten?
- Yeah, Mrs. Lustgarten. Yeah.
- Wow.
She really got me.
Yeah. Fuck, I gotta skedaddle.
Will you be careful, please?
Yeah.
Okay.
I do love you.
Even thought you left me
with the check at Pips, you dick.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Two, three, four, five,
six, seven,
eight, nine, ten,
11, 12. Shit.
Fuck.
If you want me back,
you must accommodate my needs.
I'm listening.
MDR. Non-negotiable.
Mark S. is so close
to completing Cold Harbor.
I intend to finish the work
that I started,
which is why
Milchick must go.
He's not equipped for the task.
I must be floor manager.
I hear ego...
hubris...
arrogance.
Kier teaches us they only cause pain.
Everything I accomplished, I earned...
through dedication and industry,
not because I was born into it.
I think you've overestimated
your contributions
and underestimated your blessings.
We didn't have to ask you back.
You didn't have a choice.
Are you sure?
Why don't we reset?
It doesn't have to be this way.
Natalie.
Please see if the Board is available
for Ms. Cobel and myself.
Let's go speak with them together.
Harmony.
Thirty-three, 34, 35, 36,
thirty s--
Jesus Christ.
Are you trying to burn a message
to your innie into your retinas
because your computer told you
that was a brilliant idea?
Yeah.
No, no. What? No, no, no, no, no.
What are you... What?
It doesn't work.
- No shit.
- The switch briefly dilates the pupils.
Clean slate.
- Okay, thank you. Thanks.
- Also, you could blind yourself.
And how was the innie
gonna send you a message back?
That's his problem. I don't know.
Mark, unlock the door.
Why?
We need to talk.
- Oh, my God.
- Mark, unlock the--
Mark, unlock this fucking door!
Goddamn it. This goddamn fucking thing.
- What?
- There's an easier way.
Didn't seem particularly easy for Petey.
Heard about the OTC.
Yeah, my sister talked to my innie.
He said a lot of things.
Did he tell her
your wife is alive at Lumon?
Who told you that?
Is she?
Is Gemma alive?
She was, the last time I saw her.
How could you not tell me?
We were interrupted, if you recall.
Mark, I want to help you,
but you have to trust me.
How the fu...
There is one way, and one way only,
to get information in and out of Lumon,
and that's reintegration.
I'm better at it now.
I can make it work with you.
I can sew together a version of you that
loves her with a version of you that can--
Yes. Do it.
You're sure?
I wanna see my wife.
The monitors differentiate
the five brain wave frequencies
of the innie and outie.
Delta, theta, alpha, beta, gamma.
One frequency, two waves per oscilloscope.
The waves aren't in sync. Not yet, anyway.
That's what we're here to do.
Lean forward.
Is it gonna hurt?
Ideally not.
What does your mouth taste like?
Nothing.
Good.
What the fuck?
Shit.
You all right?
I don't know. Am I?
I'm gonna start with easy questions
and get more complex.
Do you remember protocol?
- Is that the first question?
- No, we haven't started yet.
Yes, I remember.
Relax your body. You should feel good
when this is over. Who am I?
Okay, so are--
We've started. Who am I?
Asal Reghabi.
Where are we?
My basement.
What was your mother's name?
Fern Scout.
What was her eye color?
Seriously?
Brown. It was brown.
Did you love her?
Yeah.
Name a dam.
Hoover.
What does MDR stand for?
What?
MDR.
- Mystic--
- That's wrong.
What is something
for which you feel shame?
Shame.
My dog died when I was a kid.
It was my fault.
Why?
I left the gate open.
Where were you born?
I'm not sure.
What month is it?
You mean, what quarter?
Wait.
What is your first memory?
- I don't know.
- Tell me.
Holy shit.
- I don't know. I don't remember.
- Tell me.
- Tell me your first memory.
- I don't remember.
Hey there, you on the table.
I wonder if you'd mind taking
a brief survey.
Five questions.
To start out, who are you?